[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I escaped a giant rolling boulder by running through twenty feet of spider webs. Who am I?", "correct_answer": "Indiana Jones", "incorrect_answers": ["The Terminator", "John McClane", "Rambo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the sequel to 2007s Transformers?", "correct_answer": "Transformers 2 Revenge of the Fallen", "incorrect_answers": ["Transformers 2 Revenge of the Decepticons", "Transformers 2 Return of the Autobots", "Transformers 2 Return of the Transformers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Periander of Corinth, Pittacus of Mitylene and Thales of Miletus have something in common. What is it?", "correct_answer": "They are three of the Seven Sages of Greece.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are three of the most famous Greek characters.", "They are three of the Seven mathematicians of Greece.", "They are the Three princes of Greece."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is widely regarded as the father of British Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "Daniel Defoe", "incorrect_answers": ["Sir Richard Burton", "Christopher Marlowe", "Edward Ames, Duke of Harrington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2009, Thomas R. Frieden, MD assumed office as director of this agency of the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services located just outside of Atlanta, Georgia.", "correct_answer": "Centers for Disease Control  Prevention (CDC)", "incorrect_answers": ["Mayo Clinic", "Food and Drug Administration", "American Lung Association"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does a koala eat?", "correct_answer": "eucalyptus leaves", "incorrect_answers": ["banyan tree", "bamboo", "rice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Johnny Dangerously, what caliber was Danny Vermins pistol?", "correct_answer": ".88 Magnum", "incorrect_answers": [".44 Magnum", ".357 Magnum", ".45 Long Colt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following disorders is NOT a form of anxiety?", "correct_answer": "Cyclothymia", "incorrect_answers": ["Body Dysmorphic Disorder", "Somatization Disorder", "Panic Disorder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term do scientists use to denote the gradual warming of the planet due to absorption of infrared radiation by the atmosphere?", "correct_answer": "Greenhouse effect", "incorrect_answers": ["Ozone depletion", "Atmospheric termoincrease", "Global dimming"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous cat made a guest appearance in the films Shrek 2 and Shrek 3?", "correct_answer": "Puss in Boots", "incorrect_answers": ["Felix the Cat", "Tom the Cat", "Mr. Tinkles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last movie for which Katharine Hepburn won an Academy Award for Best Actress?", "correct_answer": "On Golden Pond", "incorrect_answers": ["Guess Whos Coming to Dinner", "The Lion in Winter", "Morning Glory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Work expands to fill the time available for its completion. Under what name is this law known?", "correct_answer": "Parkinsons Law", "incorrect_answers": ["Atkinsons Law", "Pattersons Law", "Robinsons Law"]}]